{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074537711","data":{"timestamp":" 947074537711"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151524"," gameId":" 41c24545-af8e-45d6-ad81-fa2b38ee617e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074537935","data":{"timestamp":" 947074537935"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151524"," gameId":" 41c24545-af8e-45d6-ad81-fa2b38ee617e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074538897","data":{"timestamp":" 947074538897"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151524"," gameId":" 41c24545-af8e-45d6-ad81-fa2b38ee617e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074540170","data":{"timestamp":" 947074540170"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151524"," gameId":" 41c24545-af8e-45d6-ad81-fa2b38ee617e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074543044","data":{"timestamp":" 947074543044"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151524"," gameId":" 41c24545-af8e-45d6-ad81-fa2b38ee617e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074543888","data":{"timestamp":" 947074543888"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151524"," gameId":" 41c24545-af8e-45d6-ad81-fa2b38ee617e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074544201","data":{"timestamp":" 947074544201"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151524"," gameId":" 41c24545-af8e-45d6-ad81-fa2b38ee617e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074545488","data":{"timestamp":" 947074545488"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151524"," gameId":" 41c24545-af8e-45d6-ad81-fa2b38ee617e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074548984","data":{"timestamp":" 947074548984"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151524"," gameId":" 41c24545-af8e-45d6-ad81-fa2b38ee617e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074549987","data":{"timestamp":" 947074549986"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151524"," gameId":" 41c24545-af8e-45d6-ad81-fa2b38ee617e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074550241","data":{"timestamp":" 947074550240"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151524"," gameId":" 41c24545-af8e-45d6-ad81-fa2b38ee617e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074550528","data":{"timestamp":" 947074550527"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151524"," gameId":" 41c24545-af8e-45d6-ad81-fa2b38ee617e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074550615","data":{"timestamp":" 947074550615"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151524"," gameId":" 41c24545-af8e-45d6-ad81-fa2b38ee617e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074563355","data":{"timestamp":" 947074563355"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151524"," gameId":" 2717cb9b-6b82-402b-b122-39493ed1229a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaitwa Bi Simu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAITWA"," userResponse":" ANAITWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074563668","data":{"timestamp":" 947074563667"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151524"," gameId":" 2717cb9b-6b82-402b-b122-39493ed1229a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaitwa Bi Simu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BI"," userResponse":" BI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074564270","data":{"timestamp":" 947074564270"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151524"," gameId":" 2717cb9b-6b82-402b-b122-39493ed1229a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaitwa Bi Simu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074567885","data":{"timestamp":" 947074567885"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151524"," gameId":" 2717cb9b-6b82-402b-b122-39493ed1229a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaitwa Bi Simu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANAITWA"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074569003","data":{"timestamp":" 947074569003"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151524"," gameId":" 2717cb9b-6b82-402b-b122-39493ed1229a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaitwa Bi Simu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAITWA"," userResponse":" ANAITWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074572044","data":{"timestamp":" 947074572043"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151524"," gameId":" 2717cb9b-6b82-402b-b122-39493ed1229a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaitwa Bi Simu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074573863","data":{"timestamp":" 947074573862"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151524"," gameId":" 2717cb9b-6b82-402b-b122-39493ed1229a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaitwa Bi Simu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074576064","data":{"timestamp":" 947074576064"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151524"," gameId":" 2717cb9b-6b82-402b-b122-39493ed1229a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwangalie!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANGALIE"," userResponse":" MWANGALIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074581056","data":{"timestamp":" 947074581056"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151524"," gameId":" 2717cb9b-6b82-402b-b122-39493ed1229a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwangalie!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANGALIE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074583230","data":{"timestamp":" 947074583229"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151524"," gameId":" 2717cb9b-6b82-402b-b122-39493ed1229a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074583877","data":{"timestamp":" 947074583877"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151524"," gameId":" 2717cb9b-6b82-402b-b122-39493ed1229a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074584641","data":{"timestamp":" 947074584641"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151524"," gameId":" 2717cb9b-6b82-402b-b122-39493ed1229a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074587212","data":{"timestamp":" 947074587212"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151524"," gameId":" 2717cb9b-6b82-402b-b122-39493ed1229a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074589775","data":{"timestamp":" 947074589775"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151524"," gameId":" 2717cb9b-6b82-402b-b122-39493ed1229a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074591716","data":{"timestamp":" 947074591716"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151524"," gameId":" 2717cb9b-6b82-402b-b122-39493ed1229a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074593959","data":{"timestamp":" 947074593959"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151524"," gameId":" 2717cb9b-6b82-402b-b122-39493ed1229a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIAMKA"," userResponse":" AKIAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074595561","data":{"timestamp":" 947074595561"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151524"," gameId":" 2717cb9b-6b82-402b-b122-39493ed1229a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAZIPANGA"," userResponse":" ANAZIPANGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074596177","data":{"timestamp":" 947074596176"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151524"," gameId":" 2717cb9b-6b82-402b-b122-39493ed1229a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074596867","data":{"timestamp":" 947074596867"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151524"," gameId":" 2717cb9b-6b82-402b-b122-39493ed1229a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074597711","data":{"timestamp":" 947074597711"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151524"," gameId":" 2717cb9b-6b82-402b-b122-39493ed1229a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074598639","data":{"timestamp":" 947074598639"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151524"," gameId":" 2717cb9b-6b82-402b-b122-39493ed1229a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074598768","data":{"timestamp":" 947074598768"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151524"," gameId":" 2717cb9b-6b82-402b-b122-39493ed1229a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074599289","data":{"timestamp":" 947074599289"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151524"," gameId":" 2717cb9b-6b82-402b-b122-39493ed1229a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MEZA"," userResponse":" MEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074605332","data":{"timestamp":" 947074605332"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151524"," gameId":" 2717cb9b-6b82-402b-b122-39493ed1229a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIAMKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074607677","data":{"timestamp":" 947074607677"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151524"," gameId":" 2717cb9b-6b82-402b-b122-39493ed1229a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAZIPANGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074609797","data":{"timestamp":" 947074609797"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151524"," gameId":" 2717cb9b-6b82-402b-b122-39493ed1229a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074611931","data":{"timestamp":" 947074611931"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151524"," gameId":" 2717cb9b-6b82-402b-b122-39493ed1229a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074615664","data":{"timestamp":" 947074615664"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151524"," gameId":" 2717cb9b-6b82-402b-b122-39493ed1229a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074616333","data":{"timestamp":" 947074616333"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151524"," gameId":" 2717cb9b-6b82-402b-b122-39493ed1229a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074616543","data":{"timestamp":" 947074616543"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151524"," gameId":" 2717cb9b-6b82-402b-b122-39493ed1229a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074639032","data":{"timestamp":" 947074639031"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151524"," gameId":" 108854b9-8a08-4af9-894f-255924d55af5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_0+6"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074647395","data":{"timestamp":" 947074647395"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151524"," gameId":" 108854b9-8a08-4af9-894f-255924d55af5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_0+6"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074647429","data":{"timestamp":" 947074647428"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151524"," gameId":" 108854b9-8a08-4af9-894f-255924d55af5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_0+6"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}